{
    "Education": [
        {"question": "Do you have a bachelor's degree or higher?", "answer": "Yes"},
        {"question": "What is your highest level of education?", "answer": "Bachelor's degree"}
    ],
    "Leadership Experience": [
        {"question": "Do you have team leadership experience?", "answer": "No"},
        {"question": "Have you previously managed a team?", "answer": "No"}
    ],
    "Programming Experience": [
        {"question": "How many years have you worked with Python?", "answer": "3 years"},
        {"question": "How many years have you worked with React?", "answer": "1 Year"},
        {"question": "How many years of expereience do you have with Software Development?", "answer": "3 years"},
        {"question": "How many years of professional development experience do you have?", "answer": "2 years"},
        {"question": "How many years of professional experience do you have with PostgreSQL?", "answer": "2 years"},
        {"question": "How many years of professional experience do you have with SQL?", "answer": "4 years"},
        {"question": "How many years of work experience do you have with JavaScript Frameworks?", "answer": "3 years"},
        {"question": "State your experience duration with C#.", "answer": "2 years"}
    ],
    "Programming Languages": [
        {"question": "What programming languages can you work with?", "answer": "Python, JavaScript, C#"}
    ],
    "Skills Proficiency": [
        {"question": "Rate your SQL skills.", "answer": "Advanced"},
        {"question": "What is your proficiency with SQL technologies?", "answer": "Advanced"}
    ],
    "Work Authorization": [
        {"question": "Are you authorized to work in the U.S. without restriction?", "answer": "No"},
        {"question": "Are you legally authorized to work in the United States?", "answer": "Yes"},
        {"question": "Will you now or in the future require sponsorship to work within the United States?", "answer": "No"},
        {"question": "Will you now, or in the future, require sponsorship for employment visa status (e.g. H-1B visa status)?Will you now, or in the future, require sponsorship for employment visa status (e.g. H-1B visa status)?", "answer":"No"}
    ],
    "Work Preferences": [
        {"question": "Are you able to commute to our office near Bryant Park 4 times a week?", "answer":"Yes"},
        {"question": "Are you comfortable commuting to this job's location?", "answer": "Yes"},
        {"question": "Are you comfortable working in an onsite setting?", "answer": "Yes"},
        {"question": "Are you willing to take a drug test, in accordance with local law/regulations?", "answer": "Yes"},
        {"question": "Will you be able to work onsite at our Brooklyn location at least 3 days per week?", "answer": "Yes"}
    ]
}